import '../classes/quiz_class.dart';

List<QuizQuestion> aotQuestions = [
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the release date of Attack on Titan Season Two?",
      answer1: "2016",
      answer2: "2017",
      answer3: "2018",
      answer4: "2019",
      correctAnswer: "2017"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "what does Shingeki no Kyojin mean?",
      answer1: "The Attack Titan",
      answer2: "Rhe Titan",
      answer3: "The Victory",
      answer4: "Something Else",
      correctAnswer: "The Attack Titan"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "the name of first episode in AOt is? ",
      answer1: "to you, 2000 years from now",
      answer2: "The Fall of Shiganshina, Part 2",
      answer3: "A Dim Light Amid Despair: Humanity's Comeback, Part 1",
      answer4: "he Night of the Closing Ceremony",
      correctAnswer: "to you, 2000 years from now"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "what is the nationality of levi",
      answer1: "German",
      answer2: "French",
      answer3: "British",
      answer4: "Japanese",
      correctAnswer: "German"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "how many titan are there?",
      answer1: "Eleven",
      answer2: "Twelve",
      answer3: "Thirteen",
      answer4: "Fourteen",
      correctAnswer: "Thirteen"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the real name of crista?",
      answer1: "Historia",
      answer2: "Mera",
      answer3: "Sarah",
      answer4: "Mony",
      correctAnswer: "Historia"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who killed reiss famly?",
      answer1: "Grisha jeager",
      answer2: "Eren jeager",
      answer3: "Frieda Reiss",
      answer4: "Marley",
      correctAnswer: "Grisha jeager"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "In which way eren aunt died?",
      answer1: "Eaten by a titan",
      answer2: "Killed by a soldier",
      answer3: "Suicided ",
      answer4: "Eaten by a dog",
      correctAnswer: "Eaten by a dog"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "From whom is the cloth on levi's neck?",
      answer1: "From his mom clothes",
      answer2: "A gift",
      answer3: "Bought it ",
      answer4: "None of the above",
      correctAnswer: "From his mom clothes"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "How many titan eren kill?",
      answer1: "One",
      answer2: "Two",
      answer3: "Three",
      answer4: "Four",
      correctAnswer: "One"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Which one form reiss famliy that visits krista?",
      answer1: "Grisha jeager",
      answer2: "Eren jeager",
      answer3: "Frieda Reiss",
      answer4: "Marly",
      correctAnswer: "Frieda Reiss"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the name of the island in attack on titan?",
      answer1: "Paradise",
      answer2: "Freedom",
      answer3: "Eldia",
      answer4: "Hell",
      correctAnswer: "Paradise"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who is the youngest soldier of the 104th Cadet Corps?",
      answer1: "Mikasa",
      answer2: "Reiner",
      answer3: "Annie",
      answer4: "Historia",
      correctAnswer: "Historia"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "How often does the Scout Regiment usually go outside the walls on an expedition?",
      answer1: "About Once a Month",
      answer2: "About Twice a Month",
      answer3: "Twice a week",
      answer4: "Once a day",
      correctAnswer: "About Once a Month"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Eren, Mikasa, and Armin saw a soldier who reminded them of who?",
      answer1: "Hannes",
      answer2: "Levi",
      answer3: "Annie",
      answer4: "Historia",
      correctAnswer: "Hannes"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who was noted to be always sweating by others?",
      answer1: "Bertholdt",
      answer2: "Levi",
      answer3: "Historia",
      answer4: "Annie",
      correctAnswer: "Bertholdt"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who was noted to be always sweating by others?",
      answer1: "Bertholdt",
      answer2: "Levi",
      answer3: "Historia",
      answer4: "Annie",
      correctAnswer: "Bertholdt"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Eren went berserk and fought Annie. Who made her fall from the Wall as she tried to escape?",
      answer1: "Mikasa",
      answer2: "Levi",
      answer3: "Eren",
      answer4: "Jean",
      correctAnswer: "Mikasa"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What's the name of the original opening song?",
      answer1: "Shingeki no Kyojin",
      answer2: "Sasageyo",
      answer3: "Silhouette",
      answer4: "None of the Above",
      correctAnswer: "Silhouette"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who was the commander before Erwin?",
      answer1: "Levi Ackerman",
      answer2: "keith shadies",
      answer3: "Sasha Blouse",
      answer4: "None of the Above",
      correctAnswer: "keith shadies"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is Levi's last name?",
      answer1: "Ackerman",
      answer2: "Shadies",
      answer3: "Blouse",
      answer4: "Ral",
      correctAnswer: "Ackerman"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "How the gaint titan protect himself?",
      answer1: "Steam released from his body",
      answer2: "Puts Armor on his body",
      answer3: "All of The Above",
      answer4: "None of The Above",
      correctAnswer: "Steam released from his body"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who taught Levi everything he knows?",
      answer1: "Kenny",
      answer2: "Karla",
      answer3: "Freida",
      answer4: "Krista",
      correctAnswer: "Kenny"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who is known as the \"Potato Girl?\"",
      answer1: "Mikasa",
      answer2: "Historia",
      answer3: "Anne",
      answer4: "Sasha",
      correctAnswer: "Sasha"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who is the identity of the smiling titan?",
      answer1: "The first wife of Grisha",
      answer2: "Reiner",
      answer3: "Anne",
      answer4: "Yamir",
      correctAnswer: "The first wife of Grisha"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "what is the name of the three walls?",
      answer1: "Sina, Rose and Maria",
      answer2: "Sina, Mary, Rose",
      answer3: "Rose, Mira, Sina",
      answer4: "None of the Above",
      correctAnswer: "Sina, Rose and Maria"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who was responsible for messing up Eren's equipment during their training period?",
      answer1: "Keith",
      answer2: "Levi",
      answer3: "Reiner",
      answer4: "Anne",
      correctAnswer: "Keith"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Why don't the Wall Titans move?",
      answer1: "The lack of sunlight",
      answer2: "Not Enough Food",
      answer3: "Didn't reeive an Order",
      answer4: "All of the Above",
      correctAnswer: "Keith"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "How many titan known that can be human again?",
      answer1: "Seven",
      answer2: "Eight",
      answer3: "Nine",
      answer4: "Ten",
      correctAnswer: "Nine"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "When crista punches Levi, how does he react?",
      answer1: "He Smiled",
      answer2: "He Punhed her Back",
      answer3: "He Cried",
      answer4: "He Shouted",
      correctAnswer: "He Smiled"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who the one that gave the idea to crista to punche levi?",
      answer1: "Mikasa",
      answer2: "Anne",
      answer3: "Eren",
      answer4: "Reiner",
      correctAnswer: "Mikasa"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the outermost wall protecting the humans called?",
      answer1: "Wall Maria",
      answer2: "Wall Rose",
      answer3: "Wall Sina",
      answer4: "Will Mira",
      correctAnswer: "Wall Maria"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Mikasa's mother was from Germany and her father was from ..",
      answer1: "Japan",
      answer2: "France",
      answer3: "Russia",
      answer4: "England",
      correctAnswer: "Japan"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What does Annie do when she is captured?",
      answer1: "crystallizes",
      answer2: "Screams",
      answer3: "Emits Steam",
      answer4: "None of The Above",
      correctAnswer: "crystallizes"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who is NOT ranked in the top ten of the Southern Division in the 104th Training Corps?",
      answer1: "Armin",
      answer2: "Eren",
      answer3: "Mikasa",
      answer4: "Anne",
      correctAnswer: "Armin"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the dream of armain and eren?",
      answer1: "To See the Ocean",
      answer2: "To Kill Titans",
      answer3: "To Bring Peace",
      answer4: "To Rank Up",
      correctAnswer: "To See the Ocean"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the name of eren's mother?",
      answer1: "Carla",
      answer2: "Marie",
      answer3: "Anna",
      answer4: "Jona",
      correctAnswer: "Carla"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who is the one that brought up armin after his family's death?",
      answer1: "His Grandfather",
      answer2: "His Grandmother",
      answer3: "His Friends",
      answer4: "The Neighbors",
      correctAnswer: "His Grandfather"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "what is the name of the one that has all the titan and named as the Goddess of titan?",
      answer1: "Yamir",
      answer2: "Anna",
      answer3: "Mikasa",
      answer4: "None of The Above",
      correctAnswer: "Yamir"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the name of the royal family?",
      answer1: "Reiss",
      answer2: "Arlert",
      answer3: "Ackerman",
      answer4: "Yeager",
      correctAnswer: "Reiss"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "what is the name of eren's brother?",
      answer1: "Zake",
      answer2: "Reiner",
      answer3: "Zika",
      answer4: "Zino",
      correctAnswer: "Zake"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "who says this quate \"you must save miksa and aramin\"?",
      answer1: "Eren",
      answer2: "Reiner",
      answer3: "Levi",
      answer4: "Anne",
      correctAnswer: "Eren"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "who says this quate \"you must save miksa and aramin\"?",
      answer1: "Eren",
      answer2: "Reiner",
      answer3: "Levi",
      answer4: "Anne",
      correctAnswer: "Eren"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the other abilty of the beast titan?",
      answer1: "Controls The Titans",
      answer2: "Throws Projectiles",
      answer3: "Emits steam",
      answer4: "Puts Armor",
      correctAnswer: "Controls The Titans"
  ),
];